1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. custom.BrowserHelper.closeFirefoxPopup()
17. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-create-new-account"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Email"), "agung.priyadi@gtech.digital")
25. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
29. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
33. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-sign-up"))
37. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Registration/verify-duplicate-email"), "The mobile or email already exist.")
41. takeScreenshot()
45. closeBrowser()